HERE Official Journals on Microfilm. 6199/011 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
HERE Official Journals on Microfilm
1896-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
6199/011 mf
3.11 cubic feet
28 microfilm reels
Publications, convention proceedings, microfilm.
8255113
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
R. Miles, February 07, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 07, 2013
Scope and Contents
Includes volumes of American Caterer (1896), The National Purveyor (1897-1899), The Mixer and Server (1900-1929), and The Catering Industry Employee (1929-1982). Also included are proceedings from 36th "Diamond Jubilee" General Convention (1966).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (HERE)
8255113
- American Caterer. Vol. 1, 1896; 1 (Reel 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Beginning at frame 0005.
- The National Purveyor. Vol. 1, 1897; 2 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at frame 0060.
- The National Purveyor. Vol. 2, 1898; 3 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at frame 0096.
- The National Purveyor. Vol. 3, 1899; 4 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at frame 0137.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 9, 1900; 5 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at frame 0179.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 10, 1901; 6 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at frame 0407.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 11, 1902; 7 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at frame 0674.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 12, 1903; 8 (Reel 1)
  Beginning at frame 0915.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 13, 1904; 1 (Reel 2)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 14, 1905; 2 (Reel 2)
  Beginning at frame 0867.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 15, 1906; 3 (Reel 2)
  Beginning at frame 1529.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 16, 1907; 1 (Reel 3)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 17, 1908; 2 (Reel 3)
  Beginning at frame 0729.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 18, 1909; 3 (Reel 3)
  Beginning at frame 1407.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 19, 1910; 1 (Reel 4)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 20, 1911; 2 (Reel 4)
  Beginning at frame 0713.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 21, 1912; 3 (Reel 4)
  Beginning at frame 1639.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 22, 1913; 1 (Reel 5)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 23, 1914; 2 (Reel 5)
  Beginning at frame 1008.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 24, 1915; 1 (Reel 6)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 25, 1916; 2 (Reel 6)
  Beginning at frame 1102.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 26, 1917; 1 (Reel 7)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 27, 1918; 2 (Reel 7)
  Beginning at frame 1060.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 28, 1919; 1 (Reel 8)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 29, 1920; 2 (Reel 8)
  Beginning at frame 1188.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 30, 1921; 1 (Reel 9)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 31, 1922; 2 (Reel 9)
  Beginning at frame 1053.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 32, 1923; 1 (Reel 10)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 33, 1924; 2 (Reel 10)
  Beginning at frame 1011.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 34, 1925; 1 (Reel 11)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 35, 1926; 2 (Reel 11)
  Beginning at frame 1017.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 36, 1927; 1 (Reel 12)
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 37, 1928; 2 (Reel 12)
  Beginning at frame 1163.
- The Mixer and Server. Vol. 38 and The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 38, 1929; 1 (Reel 13)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 39, 1930; 2 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at frame 0743.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 40, 1931; 3 (Reel 13)
  Beginning at frame 1322.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 41, 1932; 1 (Reel 14)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 42, 1933; 2 (Reel 14)
  Beginning at frame 0618.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 43, 1934; 3 (Reel 14)
  Beginning at frame 1068.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 44, 1935; 1 (Reel 15)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 45, 1936; 2 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at frame 0598.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 46, 1937; 3 (Reel 15)
  Beginning at frame 1460.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 47, 1938; 1 (Reel 16)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 48, 1939; 2 (Reel 16)
  Beginning at frame 1697.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 49, 1940; 1 (Reel 17)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 50, 1941; 2 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at frame 0680.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 51, 1942; 3 (Reel 17)
  Beginning at frame 1616.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 52, 1943; 1 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at frame 0006.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 53, 1944; 2 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at frame 0677.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 54, 1945; 3 (Reel 18)
  Beginning at frame 1282.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 55, 1946; 1 (Reel 19)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 56, 1947; 2 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at frame 0579.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 57, 1948; 3 (Reel 19)
  Beginning at frame 1400.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 58, 1949; 1 (Reel 20)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 59, 1950; 2 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at frame 0497.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 60, 1951; 3 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at frame 989.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 61, 1952; 4 (Reel 20)
  Beginning at frame 1486.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 62, 1953; 1 (Reel 21)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 63, 1954; 2 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at frame 0520.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 64, 1955; 3 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at frame 1018.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 65, 1956; 4 (Reel 21)
  Beginning at frame 1477.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 66, 1957; 1 (Reel 22)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 67, 1958; 2 (Reel 22)
  Beginning at frame 0861.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 68, 1959; 3 (Reel 22)
  Beginning at frame 1346.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 69, 1960; 1 (Reel 23)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 70, 1961; 2 (Reel 23)
  Beginning at frame 0524.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 71, 1962; 3 (Reel 23)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 72, 1963; 1 (Reel 24)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 73, 1964; 2 (Reel 24)
  Beginning at frame 0522.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 74, 1965; 3 (Reel 24)
  Beginning at frame 1032.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 75, 1966; 4 (Reel 24)
  Beginning at frame 1539.
- Proceedings of the 36th General Convention, 1966; 1 (Reel 25)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 76, 1967; 2 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at frame 0273.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 77, 1968; 3 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at frame 0785.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 78, 1969; 4 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at frame 1307.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 79, 1970; 5 (Reel 25)
  Beginning at frame 1824.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 80, 1971; 1 (Reel 26)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 81, 1972; 2 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at frame 0771.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 82, 1973; 3 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at frame 1281.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 83, 1974; 4 (Reel 26)
  Beginning at frame 1835.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 84, 1975; 1 (Reel 27)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 85, 1976; 2 (Reel 27)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 86, 1977; 3 (Reel 27)
  Beginning at frame 1213.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 87, 1978; 4 (Reel 27)
  Beginning at frame 1604.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 88, 1979; 1 (Reel 28)
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 89, 1980; 2 (Reel 28)
  Beginning at frame 0389.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 90, 1981; 3 (Reel 28)
  Beginning at frame 0773.
- The Catering Industry Employee. Vol. 91, 1982; 4 (Reel 28)
  Beginning at frame 1498.